const questions = [{'question': 'What is the Anti-Defection Law?', 'options': ['A law against corruption', 'Ban on political parties', 'Prohibition of hate speech', 'Disqualification of members who defect'], 'correctAnswer': 3, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'Which amendment introduced the Anti-Defection Law in the Indian Constitution?', 'options': ['42nd Amendment', '52nd Amendment', '73rd Amendment', '91st Amendment'], 'correctAnswer': 1, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'Under the Anti-Defection Law a member of a house can be disqualified if they voluntarily give up their membership of a political party', 'options': ['True', 'False', 'Both', 'NoneoftheAbove'], 'correctAnswer': 0, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'Who is the final authority to decide on a disqualification under the Anti-Defection Law?', 'options': ['President of India', 'Prime Minister', 'Chief Justice of India', 'Speaker of the House'], 'correctAnswer': 3, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'The Anti-Defection Law applies to which of the following legislatures?', 'options': ['Lok Sabha (Lower House)', 'Rajya Sabha (Upper House)', 'State Legislative Assemblies', 'All of the above'], 'correctAnswer': 3, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'What is the minimum number of members required to split a legislative party for Anti-Defection Law to apply?', 'options': ['1/6 of total members', '1/3 of total members', 'Half of the total members', '2/3 of total members'], 'correctAnswer': 1, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'In how many days should the Speaker decide on a disqualification petition under the Anti-Defection Law?', 'options': ['15 days', '30 days', '45 days', '60 days'], 'correctAnswer': 1, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'Which case led to the landmark judgment by the Supreme Court that gave powers to the Speaker to decide disqualification matters?', 'options': ['S.R. Bommai case', 'Indira Nehru Gandhi case', 'Kihoto Hollohan case', 'T.M.A. Pai case'], 'correctAnswer': 2, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'What is the maximum duration a member can be suspended under the Anti-Defection Law?', 'options': ['30 days', '60 days', '90 days', '120 days'], 'correctAnswer': 2, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}, {'question': 'Who proposed the inclusion of the Anti-Defection Law in the Indian Constitution?', 'options': ['B.R. Ambedkar', 'Hemwati Nandan Bahuguna', 'Rajiv Gandhi', 'P.V. Narasimha Rao'], 'correctAnswer': 1, 'userAnswerIndex': -1}];
